I don't know if we live in a nation today that often the last time we turned to a sprayer.
If all that sprayer right now is that you were just blessed this meeting.
We're glad I prayed that there would be fruit to be straight forward from the fact that they have to decide
for some of the hope in the meeting prayer.
I've got to bless everything that they need to do.
I pray for wisdom over the people that run this town.
For God I pray that they would have a love for my amma, such as I do.
Or that I just want to thank you for the hearts.
I want to thank you for the minds, like the city of Myomo,
hopeful, hopeful, and a great blessing that we reach to everyone.
I pray all of this in the year, so I'm Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Thank you.
Second.
Forster.
All right.
What's this?
I don't know.
All right.
I'm living on the bridge.
Thank you.
None of this is in the cave.
You know that?
That's a quarter of somebody.
Thank you.
For sure.
For us in Los Angeles.